邪恶力量前情提要
Previously on Supernatural...
那晚发生的事
What happened that night
赶快带你弟弟出去
Take your brother outside as fast as you can!
快 迪恩 快跑
Now Dean! Go!
他们亲眼目睹
What they witnessed
玛丽 不
Mary! No!
两兄弟
Sent two brothers
爸爸已经踏上了捕猎之旅
Dad's on a hunting trip.
他好几天没回家了
And he hasn't been home in a few days.
杰西 失陪一下
Jess excuse us.
从此踏上征途 22年后
On a quest for answers. 22 years later
我发过誓我再也不猎魔了
I swore I was done hunting,
永远不
For good.
我一个人干不了
I can't do this alone.
你三更半夜要突然离开
Now you're taking off the middle of the night
跑去跟他们共度周末吗
to spend the week end with them.
不会有事的
Hey, everything's gonna be OK.
我保证
I promise.
你认为妈妈希望我们这样生活吗
You think mom would have wanted this for us?
迪恩 我们像战士一样被养大
Dean, we were raised like warriors.
你有责任
You have a responsability.
对老爸还有他那猎魔运动吗
To dad and his crusade.
就算我们找到杀死妈妈的凶手
Even if you do find the thing that killed her,
她也已经死了 回不来了
Mom's gone and she isn't coming back.
别这样说她
Don't talk about her like that.
老爸走了
Dad's gone.
我有他的日记 他留下了一些信息
I've got his journal. He left me a message.
他给我们留的这些坐标 真奇怪
It's coordinates he left us. It's weird, man.
迪恩
Hey, Dean,
我之前说的话
What I said earlier,
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
现在不是煽情的时候
No chick flick moments.
杰西
Jess.
不
No!
我们有活要干了
We got work to do.
《邪恶力量》
(黑水山脉 科罗拉多州 失落溪)
老兄 你在作弊
Dude, you're cheating.
不 是你太烂了
No, you just suck.
你好 海莉 今天是第六天
Hey, Hailey. Day six.
我们还待在黑水山脉
We're still out near Black Water Ridge.
我们很好 也很安全 不用担心
We're fine, keeping safe, so don't worry.
明天再联系
Talk to you tomorrow.
你去哪 我正赢得爽呢
Hey, where you going? My moment of victory.
上厕所
Nature calls.
布拉德
Brad?
加里 怎么回事
Gary, what's going on?
(加州帕洛 阿尔托市)
我…
I am, um...
你总说你不喜欢玫瑰 所以我带了这个
You always said roses were lame, so, I brought you, uh...
杰西
Jess...
噢 天哪
Oh, god.
我应该保护好你的
I should have protected you.
我应该告诉你真相的
I should have told you the truth.
你还好吗
You okay?
我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
又做恶梦了吗
Another nightmare?
想开会车吗
Want to drive for a while?
你这辈子从没这么问过我
In your whole life, you never once asked me that.
只是觉得你可能想开 不开算了
Just thought you might want to. Never mind.
伙计
Look, man,
你很担心我 我明白
You're worried about me. I get it, and...
谢谢你 但我很好
Thank you, but I'm perfectly okay.
好了 我们到哪了
All right. Where are we?
我们在格兰姜欣附近
We are just outside of Grand Junction.
知道吗
You know what?
也许我们不该那么早就离开斯坦福
Maybe we shouldn't have left Stanford so soon.
萨姆 我们在那查了好几周了
Sam, we dug around there for a week.
却一无所获
We came up with nothing.
如果你想找到杀害杰西卡的凶手
If you want to find the thing that killed Jessica...
就要先找到老爸
Got to find dad first.
老爸消失 二十年后这东西又再次出现
Dad disappearing, and this thing showing up again after 20 years?
这不仅仅是巧合
It's no coincidence.
老爸肯定知道怎么回事
Dad will have answers.
- 他知道该怎么办 - 真是奇怪
- He'll know what to do. - It's weird, man.
他留给我们的这些坐标 这个黑水山脉
These coordinates he left us, this Black Water Ridge...
- 怎么了 - 那里什么都没有
- What about it? - There's nothing there.
只有一片森林
It's just woods.
他为什么要我们去这种鬼地方
Why is he sending us to the middle of nowhere?
黑水山脉太偏远了
So Black Water Ridge is pretty remote.
它被峡谷阻隔 地形复杂 丛林密布
It's cut off by these canyons here rough terrain, dense forest,
附近都是废弃的金银矿山
Abandoned silver and gold mines all over the place...
老兄 快看看这熊有多大
Dude, check out the size of this frigging bear.
还有一群灰熊在那片区域栖息
And a dozen or more grizzlies in the area.
可以肯定那里不是远足的好去处
It's no nature hike, that's for sure.
你们不会碰巧要去黑水山脉吧
You boys aren't planning to go out near Black Water Ridge, by any chance?
不 先生
Oh, no, sir.
我们是博尔德大学环境系的学生
We're environmental study majors from U.C. boulder...
是为了论文的
just working on a paper.
关于回收利用的
Recycle, man.
屁话
Bull.
你们是那个叫海莉的女孩的朋友吧
You're friends with that Hailey girl, right?
是的
Yes.
是的 我们是
Yes, we are.
威尔金森护林员
Ranger... Wilkinson.
我把跟她说的话再跟你们说一次
Well, I will tell you exactly what I told her.
她弟弟出示了露营许可
Her brother filled out a backcountry permit
说他一直要在黑水山脉呆到二十四号
saying he wouldn't be back from Black Water until the 24th.
所以他现在还不算是失踪人口 不是吗
So it's not exactly a missing persons now, is it?
告诉那女孩不要再担心了
Tell that girl to quit worrying.
我保证他弟弟没事
I'm sure her brother's just fine.
我们会的
We will.
是海莉太猴急了
Well, that Hailey girl's quite a pistol, huh?
有过之而无不及
That is putting it mildly.
如果我们能拿那份证明的复印件
Actually, you know what would help is
给她看看 那就更好了
if I could show her a copy of that backcountry permit.
这样她就知道他弟弟什么时候回去了
You know, so she could see her brother's return date.
你是跑来泡妞的吗
What, are you cruising for a hookup or something?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
我们已经有了坐标
The coordinates point to Black Water Ridge.
还在等什么
So what are we waiting for?
我们直接去找老爸 去找这个女孩干嘛
Let's just go find dad. Why even talk to this girl?
我不知道 也许去之前
I don't know, maybe we should know
我们应该调查好情况
what we're walking into before we actually walk into it.
什么
What?
你什么时候变得怎么冲动
Since when are you all "Shoot first, ask questions later" Anyway?
现在
Since now.
真的吗
Oh, really?
你一定就是海莉·科林斯吧
You must be Hailey Collins.
我是迪恩 这是萨姆
I'm Dean, this is Sam.
我们是护林员
We're rangers with the park service.
威尔金森护林员让我们来的
Ranger Wilkinson sent us over.
我们想了解一下
We wanted to ask you some questions
你弟弟汤姆的情况
about your brother Tommy.
给我看看工作证
Let me see some I.D.
给
There you go.
- 进来吧 - 谢谢
- Come on in. - Thanks.
那是你的吗
That yours?
是的
Yeah.
车不错
Nice car.
那么 如果汤姆归期还没到
So, if Tommy's not due back for a while,
你怎么知道他是出事了
how do you know something's wrong?
他每天都打电话来报平安
He checks in every day by cell.
他会电邮照片 还有视频
He e mails photos, stupid little videos.
但是我们已经有三天没听到他的消息了
But we haven't heard anything in over three days now.
也许他手机没信号了
Well, maybe he can't get cell reception.
他还有个卫星电话
He's got a satellite phone, too.
可不可能是他玩忘形 忘记打电话了
Could it be he's just having fun and forgot to check in?
他不会的
He wouldn't do that.
我们的父母很早就过世了
Our parents are gone.
只剩下我和我两个弟弟
It's just my two brothers and me.
我们关系很密切
We all keep pretty close tabs on each other.
- 我能看看他给你发的照片吗 - 可以
- Can I see the pictures he sent you? - Yeah.
这是汤姆
That's Tommy.
你好 海莉 今天是第六天
Hey, Hailey. Day six.
我们还在黑水山脉
We're still out near Black Water Ridge.
我们很好 也很安全
We're fine, keeping safe,
不用担心 明天再联系
so don't worry, okay? Talk to you tomorrow.
我们会找到你弟弟的
We'll find your brother.
明天一早我们就去黑水山脉
We're heading out to Black Water Ridge first thing.
那也许我会在那见到你们
Then maybe I'll see you there.
听着
Look.
我不能再坐在这里傻等了
I can't sit around here anymore,
所以我雇了个向导
so I hired a guide.
我明天就出发
I'm heading out in the morning,
我要亲自找到汤姆
and I'm gonna find Tommy myself.
我知道你的感受
I think I know how you feel.
介意把这些拷给我吗
Hey, you mind forwarding these to me?
没问题
Sure.
黑水山脉没什么人烟 主要是去露营的
So, Black Water Ridge doesn't get a lot of traffic...local campers mostly...
但今年四月 还是有两个旅客失踪
but, still, this past april, two hikers went missing out there.
- 再也没有找到 - 那之前呢
- They were never found. - Any before that?
是的
Yeah.
一九八二年 八个人都失踪在那里
In 1982, eight different people all vanished in the same year.
官方说法是有灰熊袭击
Authorities said it was a grizzly attack.
还有一九五九年 和之前的一九三六年
And, again, in 1959, and again, before that, in 1936.
每二十三年一次 跟闹钟一样
Every 23 years, just like clockwork.
好了 看这个
Okay, watch this.
这是关键
Here's the clincher.
这是我拷来的汤姆的录像
I downloaded that guy tommy's video to the laptop.
看这个
Check this out.
再来一次
Do it again.
那是三帧 这是一秒的片段
That's three frames. It's a fraction of a second.
不管那东西是什么 他速度很快
Whatever that thing is, it can move.
我就说那里很邪门吧
I told you something weird was going on.
是啊 还有一件事
Yeah. I got one more thing.
五九年的时候
In '59,
有一个野营者幸存了下来
one camper survived the supposed grizzly attack,
是个小孩 勉强从森林里爬了出来
just a kid barely crawled out of the woods alive.
有他的姓名吗
Is there a name?
听着 护林员
Look, ranger,
我不知道为什么你们要问我这个
I don't know why you're asking me about this.
这事情有官方记录 我当时还是个小孩
It's public record. I was a kid.
- 我父母被一个 - 灰熊吗
- My parents got mauled by a... - grizzly?
是灰熊袭击的他们吗
That's what attacked them?
同年失踪的其他人
The other people that went missing that year,
也是灰熊袭击吗
those bear attacks, too?
那今年失踪的人呢
What about all the people that went missing this year?
也是一样吗
Same thing?
如果我们能了解我们要面对什么
If we knew what we were dealing with,
我们就有可能阻止这一切
we might be able to stop it.
我很怀疑
I seriously doubt that.
不管怎么样
Anyways,
我不觉得这有什么区别
I don't see the difference it would make.
你不会相信我
You wouldn't believe me.
没人相信
Nobody ever did.
肖先生
Mr. Shaw...
你看到什么了
what did you see?
什么都没看到
Nothing.
它移动地太快了 根本看不到
It moved too fast to see.
而且它很会隐藏
It hid too well.
我听到一些声音
I heard it, though.
咆哮声
A roar...
就像…
like...
我从没听过人或动物发出这种声音
no man or animal I ever heard.
它是晚上出现的吗
It came at night?
闯进了你的帐篷吗
Got inside your tent?
它闯进了我们的小木屋
It got inside our cabin.
它进来的时候我在壁炉前睡觉
I was sleeping in front of the fireplace when it came in.
它没有打碎窗户或者门
It didn't smash a window or break the door,
它把锁打开了
it unlocked it.
你觉得熊能开锁吗
Do you know of a bear that could do something like that?
我听到父母的尖叫才醒过来
I didn't even wake up until I heard my parents screaming.
它杀害了他们吗
It killed them?
把他们拖了出去
Dragged them off into the night.
从那以后我一直问自己
Why it left me alive...
为什么他没杀我
I've been asking myself that ever since.
但它却在我身上留下了这个
It did leave me this, though.
那森林里有很邪恶的东西
There's something evil in those woods.
它是一种魔鬼
It was some sort of a demon.
鬼魂和魔鬼不用开锁
Spirits and demons don't have to unlock doors.
他们可以穿墙而过
They just go through the walls.
所以可能是别的东西 有形的东西
So it's probably something else...something corporeal.
有形吗
"Corporeal"?
抱歉 教授
Excuse me, professor.
闭嘴 你怎么想
Shut up. So, what do you think?
那种爪子 还有移动的速度
The claws, the speed that it moves.
有可能是幻兽人 或者黑狗
It could be a skinwalker, maybe a black dog
不管是什么
Whatever we're talking about,
它一定是一种生物 是有形的
we're talking about a creature, and it's corporeal,
这意味着 我们可以杀掉它
which means we can kill it.
我们不能让海莉去那
We cannot let that Hailey girl go out there.
是吗 那我们怎么跟她解释
Oh yeah, what are we gonna tell her
因为那里有怪兽出没吗
she can't go into the woods because of a big, scary monster?
是的
Yeah.
她的弟弟失踪了 萨姆
Her brother's missing, Sam.
她不会袖手旁观的
She's not just gonna sit this out.
不 我们跟她一起去
No, we go with her,
我们一边保护她
we protect her,
一边想办法杀了那个怪物
and we keep our eyes peeled for our fuzzy predator friend
找老爸的事情还不够烦吗
So finding dad's not enough?
现在还要当保姆
Now we got to babysit, too?
怎么了
What?
没什么
Nothing.
再跟你说一次 你不该带本来这
I'll tell you again. I don't think Ben should come.
罗伊
Roy...
你付我那么多钱是为了保证大家的安全
you're paying me good money to keep everybody safe.
我觉得本还是呆在家安全
I think Ben's safest at home.
我们两个能加入吗
You guys got room for two more?
你想跟我们一起吗
You want to come with us?
这些人是谁
Who are these guys?
显然 公园就只能派这两个来了
Apparently, this is all the park service could muster up.
你们是护林员吗
You're rangers?
没错
That's right.
你们就穿着皮鞋和牛仔裤去野外吗
And you're hiking out in biker boots and jeans?
亲爱的 我从来不穿短裤
Well, sweet heart, I don't do shorts.
你们觉得这很好玩吗
Oh, you think this is funny?
偏远地区是很危险的
It's dangerous backcountry out there.
她的弟弟可能已经受伤了
Her brother might be hurt.
相信我 我知道那有多危险
Believe me, I know how dangerous it can be.
我们只想帮她找到她弟弟 如此而已
We just want to help them find their brother. That's all.
罗伊 你说你有点打猎的经验
Roy, you said you did a little hunting.
是的 不仅是有点
Yeah, more than a little.
你都打些什么动物
What kind of furry critters do you hunt?
主要是雄鹿 有时候是熊
Mostly buck. Sometimes bear.
那些动物就没复过仇吗
Tell me, uh, Bambi or Yogi ever hunt you back?
你干什么 罗伊
What you doing, Roy?
注意脚下 护林员
You should watch where you're stepping... ranger.
是捕熊夹
It's a bear trap.
你连口粮都没有带
You didn't pack any provisions.
你就带了个露营包
You guys are carrying a duffel bag.
你们不是护林员 你们到底是什么人
You're not rangers, so who the hell are you?
我和萨姆是兄弟
Sam and I are brothers,
我们在找我们老爸
and we're looking for our father.
他可能在这 我们不确定
He might be here. We don't know.
我只是觉得 我们在同一条船上
I just figured that you and me, we're in the same boat.
那你一开始怎么不告诉我
Why didn't you just tell me that from the start?
我现在不是告诉你了吗
I'm telling you now.
再说 我还从来没有对女人这么诚实过
Besides, it's probably the most honest I've ever been with a woman.
从来没有
Ever.
满意了吗
So, we okay?
那好吧
Yeah, okay.
还有 谁说我没带口粮
And what do you mean I didn't pack provisions?
就是这里
This is it.
黑水山脉
Black Water Ridge.
我们现在坐标多少
What coordinates are we at?
北纬35西经111
35 and minus 111.
听到了吗
You hear that?
是的
Yeah.
连蟋蟀都没有
Not even crickets.
我要四处转转
I'm gonna go take a look around.
你不该单独行动
You shouldn't go off by yourself.
真贴心 别担心我
That's sweet. Don't worry about me.
好了 大家都呆在一起 走吧
All right, everybody stays together. Let's go.
海莉 来这边
Hailey! Over here!
我的天
Oh, my god.
看起来像是灰熊干的
Looks like a grizzly.
汤姆
Tommy?
Tommy!
- 汤姆 - 嘘…
- Tommy! - Shh... Shh...
怎么了
Why?
这附近有东西
Something might still be out there.
萨姆
Sam.
他们被拖出了营地
The bodies were dragged from the campsite.
但到这里 踪迹就消失了
But here, the tracks just vanish.
真奇怪
It's weird.
我觉得
I tell you what.
这不是幻兽人或者黑狗干的
It's no skinwalker or black dog.
他可能还活着
Hey, he could still be alive.
救命
Help!
感觉声音是从这附近传来的 不是吗
It seemed like it was coming from around here, didn't it?
大家都回去营地
Everybody back to camp.
我们的背包
Our packs!
我的GPS和卫星手机
So much for my GPS and my satellite phone.
到底怎么回事
What the hell's going on?
它很聪明
It's smart.
它把我们与外界的联系切断
It wants to cut us off
我们就没法求救了
so we can't call for help.
你是指 有人
You mean someone...some
有个疯子把我们的东西都偷了
nut job out there just stole all our gear.
我要单独和你谈谈
I need to speak with you... in private.
好了 让我看看老爸的日记
Okay, let me see dad's journal.
好了
All right.
看这里
Check that out.
不会吧
Oh, come on.
食人魔只出没在明苏达州森林
Windigos are in the Minnesota woods
或者密西根北部
or Northern Michigan.
从来没听说他们出现在西部
I've never even heard of one this far west.
好好想想 迪恩 他们的爪子
Think about it, Dean...the claws,
模拟人的声音
the way it can mimic a human voice.
很好
Great.
那这些都没用了
Well, then this is useless.
我们得把这些人带到安全的地方
We got to get these people to safety.
好了 听着 我们要离开这里
All right, listen up. It's time to go.
事情比想象的要复杂
Things have gotten more complicated.
什么
What?
孩子 别担心
Kid, don't worry.
不管是什么 我都能搞定
Whatever's out there, I think I can handle it.
我担心的不是这个
It's not I've been worried about
如果你朝它开枪 只会激怒它
If you shoot this thing, you're just gonna make it mad.
我们必须现在离开
We have to leave now.
首先 你完全是一派胡言
One, you're talking nonsense,
其次 你没有发号施令的权利
two, you're in no position to give anybody orders.
别紧张
Relax.
我们一开始就不该让你们来这
We never should have let you come out in the first place, all right?
我是想保护你
I'm trying to protect you.
你还保护我
You protect me?
你还是个小屁孩的时候
I was hunting these woods
我就在这片森林打猎了
when your mommy was still kissing you good night.
是吗
Yeah.
这是个接近完美的猎手
It's a damn near perfect hunter.
比你更聪明
It's smarter than you.
它会抓住你 然后把你生吞活剥
And it's gonna hunt you down and eat you alive
除非我们带着你这蠢货离开这里
unless we get your stupid sorry ass out of here.
- 你疯了 - 是吗
- You know you're crazy, right? - Yeah?
- 你有捕猎过 - 冷静
- You ever hunt. - Chill out.
停 停 都别吵了
Stop! Stop it. Everybody just stop.
听着
Look.
汤姆可能还活着
Tommy might still be alive.
没有找到他我是不会离开的
And I'm not leaving here without him.
天要黑了
It's getting late.
如果说这东西在白天是个好猎手
This thing is a good hunter in the day,
到了晚上就是个不可思议的好猎手
but an unbelievable hunter at night.
晚上不可能打败它
We'll never beat it...not in the dark.
我们要找个地方保护自己
We need to settle in and protect ourselves.
怎么做
How?
- 再问一遍 那是 - 阿纳萨齐印记
- One more time.That's...? - Anasazi symbols.
是用来保护的符咒
It's for protection.
食人魔无法越过这个印记
The windigo can't cross over them.
没人喜欢无神论者 罗伊
Nobody likes a skeptic, Roy.
能告诉我你脑子里想的什么吗
You want to tell me what's going on in that freaky head of yours?
- 迪恩 - 别跟我说你没事
- Dean... - No, you're not fine.
你现在像个火药桶 你以前可不这样
You're like a powder keg, man. It's not like you.
我才是火气大的那个 记得吗
I'm supposed to be the belligerent one, remember?
老爸不在这里
Dad's not here.
这点可以肯定 是吗
I mean, that much we know for sure, right?
不然他肯定会留下线索 信息之类的
He would have left us a message, a sign, right?
是的 也许你是对的
Yeah, you're probably right.
说实话
To tell you the truth,
老爸可能根本没来过失落溪
I don't think dad's ever been to Lost Creek.
那我们就把这些人带回去
Then let's get these people back to town,
然后继续上路
and let's hit the road...
去找老爸 我们还呆在这干嘛
Go find dad. I mean, why are we still even here?
这就是为什么
This is why...
这本日记
This book.
这是老爸最珍贵的东西
This is dad's single most valuable possession.
他了解的关于恶魔的一切都记在里面
Everything he knows about every evil thing is in here.
而他把日记给了我们
And he's passed it on to us.
我觉得他希望我们继承他的事业
I think he wants us to pick up where he left off.
拯救人们 猎杀恶魔
You know, saving people, hunting things...
家族工作
The family business.
这说不通啊
That makes no sense.
为什么他连电话都不打一个
Why...why doesn't he just call us?
他怎么不告诉我们他想怎么样
Why doesn't he tell us what he wants,
他在哪里
tell us where he is?
我不知道
I don't know.
但我觉得
But the way I see it,
既然是老爸留下的活 我们就要去干
dad's given us a job to do, and I intend to do it.
迪恩
Dean...
不
No.
我要找到老爸
I gotta find dad.
我要找到杀害杰西卡的凶手
I gotta find Jessica's killer.
我脑子里只有这些
It's the only thing I can think about.
好了 萨姆
Okay. All right. Sam,
我们会找到他们的 我保证
we'll find them. I promise.
听我说
Listen to me.
你要做好准备
You've got to prepare yourself.
搜寻工作可能需要花些时间
I mean, this search could take a while.
你的那些愤怒
And all that anger,
你不能一直这样 这会要了你的命
you can't keep it burning over the long haul. It's gonna kill you.
你要有耐心
You got to have patience, man.
你怎么做到的
How do you do it?
老爸是怎么做到的
How does dad do it?
首先 为了他人
Well, for one, them.
我是指 我们家已经够惨了
I mean, I figure our family's so screwed to hell,
也许我们可以帮帮别人
maybe we can help some others.
度过难关
It makes things a little bit more bearable.
还有个解恨的办法
And I'll tell you what else helps...
尽自所能的杀掉这些恶魔
Killing as many evil sons of bitches as I possibly can.
救命
Help me!
求求你了
Please...!
救命
Help!
它想把我们引出去
It's trying to draw us out.
冷静 别动
Just stay cool. Stay put.
呆在魔法圈里吗
Inside the magic circle?
救命
Help!
救救我
Help me!
好吧 这可不是什么灰熊
Okay, that's no grizzly.
没事的 我们会没事的 我保证
It's okay. We'll be all right. I promise.
在这里
It's here.
我击中它了
I hit it!
罗伊 不要
Roy, no!
罗伊
Roy!
别动
Don't move.
它在这里
It's over here. Ugh!
罗伊
Roy?!
我不
I don't...
我是说 这些东西 不该是真的
I mean, these types of things...they aren't supposed to be real.
我也希望如此
I wish I could tell you different.
我们怎么知道他有没有监视我们
How do we know it's not out there watching us?
不知道
We don't.
但我们暂时安全
But we're safe for now.
你怎么知道这些事情的
How do you know about this stuff?
世代相传
It kind of runs in the family.
白天我们有一半的机会
So, we've got half a chance in the daylight.
首先 我自己
And I, for one...
很想杀掉这个怪物
want to kill this evil son of a bitch.
我加入
Well, hell, you know I'm in.
食人魔是印第安克里族语
Windigo is a cree indian word.
意思是贪婪的怪物
It means, "Evil that devours."
他们有上百年的历史
They're hundreds of years old.
他们以前都是人类
Each one was once a man.
印第安人 拓荒者 矿工 或是猎手
sometimes an indian or other times a frontiers manor a miner or hunter.
人类怎么会变成这种东西
How's a man turn into one of those things?
老生常谈了
Well, it's always the same.
严冬来临时
During some harsh winter,
有的人饿了 又没有补给 没有救援
a guy finds himself starving, cut off from supplies or help
于是为了生存
becomes a cannibal to survive,
杀掉了部落或者营地里的其他伙伴
eating other members of his tribe or camp.
就像多纳小队
Like the donner party.
世界上的各种文化都相信
Cultures all over the world believe
吞噬人肉可以给自身带来特殊能力
that eating human flesh gives a person certain abilities...
速度 力量 永生
speed, strength, immortality.
吞噬了足够多的同类后
If you eat enough of it,
长年累月 他们就会变成
over years, you become this...
这种半人半鬼的东西
less than human thing.
他们总是感到饥饿
You're always hungry.
如果这都是真的
So, if that's true,
汤姆怎么可能还活着
how can Tommy still be alive?
- 你不会想知道的 - 说吧
- You're not gonna like it. - Tell me.
特别的是 食人魔知道怎么度过严冬
More than anything, a windigo knows how to last long winters without food.
它有时会冬眠好几年 等它醒来
It hibernates for years at a time. When it's awake,
他会活捉一些人 把他们贮藏起来
It keeps its victims alive. It stores them
这样就可以随时进食了
so it can feed whenever it wants.
如果你弟弟还活着
If your brother's alive,
它一定把他藏在黑暗
it's keeping him somewhere dark,
隐蔽 安全的地方
hidden, and safe
我们照这个线索去找
And we got to track it back there.
到时候怎么阻止他
And then how do we stop it?
这个
Well,
枪没用 刀也是
guns are useless...so are knives.
基本上
Basically...
只能用火烧
we gotta torch the sucker.
迪恩
Dean.
怎么了
What is it?
你知道
You know,
我在想那些爪印 太过清晰明显了
I was thinking that those claw prints, so clear and distinct...
太易于追踪
They were almost too easy to follow.
- 你没事吧 - 他的脖子断了
- You okay? - His neck's broken.
跑 跑 快跑 快跑
Run, run! Go, go, go, go, go!
快 我抓住你了 我抓住你了
Come on. I got you. I got you.
海莉
Hailey!
迪恩
Dean!
如果他要活捉的话
if it keeps its victims alive,
为什么会杀了罗伊
why would it kill Roy?
说实话
Honestly?
因为罗伊朝他开枪 把他惹恼了
I think because Roy shot at it, he pissed it off.
他们朝这边走了
They went this way.
这比用面包屑引路好多了
It's better than bread crumbs.
禁止入内
Keep out, no admittance
没事的 没事的 没事的
Hey, it's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
迪恩
Dean.
快醒醒
You. Wake up.
迪恩 你还好吗
Dean. Hey. You okay?
还好
Yeah.
海莉 海莉
Hailey... Hailey.
快醒醒 快醒醒
Wake up. Wake up.
没事了
Gotcha.
- 你确定没事吗 - 是的 它在哪
- You sure you're all right? - Yeah, yeah. Where is it?
离开了
It's gone for now.
汤姆
Tommy.
把他弄下来
Cut him down.
我们会带你回家的
We're gonna get you home.
看看
Check it out.
信号枪 会有用的
Flare guns. Those will work.
看来某人回家吃饭了
Looks like someone's home for supper.
我们可跑不过它
We'll never out run it.
- 你跟我想法一样吗 - 我觉得是
- You thinking what I'm thinking? - Yeah, I think so.
好了 听我说 跟着萨姆
All right, listen to me. Stay with Sam.
他会带你们出去的
He's gonna get you out of here.
你怎么办
What are you gonna do?
来吃我吧 你这个畜生
It's chow time, you freaking bastard!
没错 放马过来吧 我味道好的很
Yeah, that's right! Bring it on, baby! I taste good!
好了 快来 快点
All right, come on. Hurry!
想来点白肉吗 畜生
Hey, you want some white meat, bitch?!
我在这呢
I'm right here!
- 快带他出去 - 萨姆 不要
- Get him out of here. - Sam, no.
快走 快走
Go. Go!
快走
Go.
来吧
Come on.
萨姆
Sam!
快跑 快 快
Come on. Hurry, hurry, hurry! Go!
躲到我身后
Get behind me.
不坏吧
Not bad, huh?
它在营地外面徘徊
That's when it circled the campsite. I mean,
那灰熊起码有八九百磅
this grizzly must have weighed 800, 900 pounds.
真不知道怎么感谢你
So, really, I don't know how to thank you.
- 别破坏了这个时刻 - 是啊
- Must you cheapen the moment? - Yeah!
- 要跟你弟弟一起走吗 - 是的
- You riding with your brother? - Yeah.
我们走吧
Let's go.
希望你早日找到你父亲
I hope you find your father.
多谢了 萨姆
Thanks, Sam.
我讨厌露营
Man, I hate camping.
我也是
Me too.
萨姆 我们会找到老爸的
Sam, you know we're gonna find dad, right?
是啊
Yeah, I know.
但这段时间…
But in the meantime...
我来开车
I'm driving.